questions:
  - question: "You are in a hotel room and you forgot the key to the door lock, but you remember your friends telling you that its first 2 even powers of 2 followed by first 2 odd powers of 3. What is the code?"
    answer: "1"
    room: "A"
    answered: false
  - question: "An Armstrong Number is a number whose sum of digits raised to the power of the number of digits equal to the number itself. If it is known that the first of this kind of number exists after the number 150. What is the first Armstrong number?"
    answer: "2"
    room: "A"
    answered: false
  - question: "A Stack is a coding construct which follows the LIFO principle (the element going in the last is the first one to come out). If the following elements are entered then what will be the first element to be outputted?"
    answer: "3"
    room: "A"
    answered: false
  - question: "If an array has 5 elements, what position would the middle element be at?"
    answer: "4"
    room: "A"
    answered: false
  - question: "A fibonacci series is a recursive series where the next element is the sum of the previous two elements with the first two elements being 0 and 1. Now Arun started the series with 2 and 10. What is the 10th element of this series?"
    answer: "5"
    room: "A"
    answered: false
  - question: "What will be the 5th element after the following is sorted according to ascii values? A b 4 f D 5 T N k n d"
    answer: "6"
    room: "A"
    answered: false
  - question: "If HEE+SHE= GIHE, and we assume (I =2), where the alphabets take the values from (0-9). Find the value of (S+H+E)?"
    answer: "7"
    room: "A"
    answered: false
  - question: "You are registering for extra courses in FFCS. You have the option of four Courses A,B,C,D. You have 4 semesters to complete all four courses. Following is a list of courses along with their prerequisites: B:A, C:A, D:B, D:C. In how many ways can the courses be taken?"
    answer: "8"
    room: "A"
    answered: false
  - question: "You are given three dice each having six faces numbered from 1 to 6 according to a regular die. What lowest combination can you get for 12? (Ex: 3: Answer: 111)"
    answer: "9"
    room: "A"
    answered: false
  - question: 'sample_set = {"Yellow", "Orange", "Black"} sample_set.update(["Blue", "Green", "Red"]) print(sample_set) How many numbers will now be in the sample test?'
    answer: "10"
    room: "A"
    answered: false

  - question: "You are in a hotel room and you forgot the key to the door lock, but you remember your friends telling you that its first 2 even powers of 2 followed by first 2 odd powers of 3. What is the code?"
    answer: "1"
    room: "B"
    answered: false
  - question: "An Armstrong Number is a number whose sum of digits raised to the power of the number of digits equal to the number itself. If it is known that the first of this kind of number exists after the number 150. What is the first Armstrong number?"
    answer: "2"
    room: "B"
    answered: false
  - question: "A Stack is a coding construct which follows the LIFO principle (the element going in the last is the first one to come out). If the following elements are entered then what will be the first element to be outputted?"
    answer: "3"
    room: "B"
    answered: false
  - question: "If an array has 5 elements, what position would the middle element be at?"
    answer: "4"
    room: "B"
    answered: false
  - question: "A fibonacci series is a recursive series where the next element is the sum of the previous two elements with the first two elements being 0 and 1. Now Arun started the series with 2 and 10. What is the 10th element of this series?"
    answer: "5"
    room: "B"
    answered: false
  - question: "What will be the 5th element after the following is sorted according to ascii values? A b 4 f D 5 T N k n d"
    answer: "6"
    room: "B"
    answered: false
  - question: "If HEE+SHE= GIHE, and we assume (I =2), where the alphabets take the values from (0-9). Find the value of (S+H+E)?"
    answer: "7"
    room: "B"
    answered: false
  - question: "You are registering for extra courses in FFCS. You have the option of four Courses A,B,C,D. You have 4 semesters to complete all four courses. Following is a list of courses along with their prerequisites: B:A, C:A, D:B, D:C. In how many ways can the courses be taken?"
    answer: "8"
    room: "B"
    answered: false
  - question: "You are given three dice each having six faces numbered from 1 to 6 according to a regular die. What lowest combination can you get for 12? (Ex: 3: Answer: 111)"
    answer: "9"
    room: "B"
    answered: false
  - question: 'sample_set = {"Yellow", "Orange", "Black"} sample_set.update(["Blue", "Green", "Red"]) print(sample_set) How many numbers will now be in the sample test?'
    answer: "10"
    room: "B"
    answered: false
  - question: "You are in a hotel room and you forgot the key to the door lock, but you remember your friends telling you that its first 2 even powers of 2 followed by first 2 odd powers of 3. What is the code?"
    answer: "1"
    room: "C"
    answered: false
  - question: "An Armstrong Number is a number whose sum of digits raised to the power of the number of digits equal to the number itself. If it is known that the first of this kind of number exists after the number 150. What is the first Armstrong number?"
    answer: "2"
    room: "C"
    answered: false
  - question: "A Stack is a coding construct which follows the LIFO principle (the element going in the last is the first one to come out). If the following elements are entered then what will be the first element to be outputted?"
    answer: "3"
    room: "C"
    answered: false
  - question: "If an array has 5 elements, what position would the middle element be at?"
    answer: "4"
    room: "C"
    answered: false
  - question: "A fibonacci series is a recursive series where the next element is the sum of the previous two elements with the first two elements being 0 and 1. Now Arun started the series with 2 and 10. What is the 10th element of this series?"
    answer: "5"
    room: "C"
    answered: false
  - question: "What will be the 5th element after the following is sorted according to ascii values? A b 4 f D 5 T N k n d"
    answer: "6"
    room: "C"
    answered: false
  - question: "If HEE+SHE= GIHE, and we assume (I =2), where the alphabets take the values from (0-9). Find the value of (S+H+E)?"
    answer: "7"
    room: "C"
    answered: false
  - question: "You are registering for extra courses in FFCS. You have the option of four Courses A,B,C,D. You have 4 semesters to complete all four courses. Following is a list of courses along with their prerequisites: B:A, C:A, D:B, D:C. In how many ways can the courses be taken?"
    answer: "8"
    room: "C"
    answered: false
  - question: "You are given three dice each having six faces numbered from 1 to 6 according to a regular die. What lowest combination can you get for 12? (Ex: 3: Answer: 111)"
    answer: "9"
    room: "C"
    answered: false
  - question: 'sample_set = {"Yellow", "Orange", "Black"} sample_set.update(["Blue", "Green", "Red"]) print(sample_set) How many numbers will now be in the sample test?'
    answer: "10"
    room: "C"
    answered: false
  - question: "You are in a hotel room and you forgot the key to the door lock, but you remember your friends telling you that its first 2 even powers of 2 followed by first 2 odd powers of 3. What is the code?"
    answer: "1"
    room: "D"
    answered: false
  - question: "An Armstrong Number is a number whose sum of digits raised to the power of the number of digits equal to the number itself. If it is known that the first of this kind of number exists after the number 150. What is the first Armstrong number?"
    answer: "2"
    room: "D"
    answered: false
  - question: "A Stack is a coding construct which follows the LIFO principle (the element going in the last is the first one to come out). If the following elements are entered then what will be the first element to be outputted?"
    answer: "3"
    room: "D"
    answered: false
  - question: "If an array has 5 elements, what position would the middle element be at?"
    answer: "4"
    room: "D"
    answered: false
  - question: "A fibonacci series is a recursive series where the next element is the sum of the previous two elements with the first two elements being 0 and 1. Now Arun started the series with 2 and 10. What is the 10th element of this series?"
    answer: "5"
    room: "D"
    answered: false
  - question: "What will be the 5th element after the following is sorted according to ascii values? A b 4 f D 5 T N k n d"
    answer: "6"
    room: "D"
    answered: false
  - question: "If HEE+SHE= GIHE, and we assume (I =2), where the alphabets take the values from (0-9). Find the value of (S+H+E)?"
    answer: "7"
    room: "D"
    answered: false
  - question: "You are registering for extra courses in FFCS. You have the option of four Courses A,B,C,D. You have 4 semesters to complete all four courses. Following is a list of courses along with their prerequisites: B:A, C:A, D:B, D:C. In how many ways can the courses be taken?"
    answer: "8"
    room: "D"
    answered: false
  - question: "You are given three dice each having six faces numbered from 1 to 6 according to a regular die. What lowest combination can you get for 12? (Ex: 3: Answer: 111)"
    answer: "9"
    room: "D"
    answered: false
  - question: 'sample_set = {"Yellow", "Orange", "Black"} sample_set.update(["Blue", "Green", "Red"]) print(sample_set) How many numbers will now be in the sample test?'
    answer: "10"
    room: "D"
    answered: false
